The Deep End of Horror!
Shock Waves is a horror, science fiction, war film directed by Ken Wiederhorn.
Visitors to a remote island discover that a reclusive Nazi
commandant has been breeding a group of zombie soldiers.
SS Commander, played by Peter Cushing.
Captain, played by John Carradine.
Rose, played by Brooke Adams.
Chuck, played by Fred Buch.
Norman, played by Jack Davidson.
Keith, played by Luke Halpin.
Shock Waves is a 1977 American horror film written
and directed by Ken Wiederhorn.
The film is about a group of tourists who encounter aquatic
Nazi zombies when they become shipwrecked.
It stars Peter Cushing as a former SS commander, Brooke Adams as a tourist,
and John Carradine as the captain of the tourists' boat.
The film explores themes of nazi, zombie, campy, deserted island.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.